http://www.corneliuslaw.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This statement applies to the online collection of personal information via websites operated by and applications offered by Schwartz Injury Law. Details of the Privacy Statement follow immediately below.
What personal information is collected and how is that information used?
We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user (such as when ordering a product, registering an account or signing up for a newsletter), from our Web server logs, and through cookies.
We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you.
We do not share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Statement, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
How is my personal information protected?
We have implemented certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.
However, please note that we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.
Also, please note that we may store and process your personal information in systems located outside of your home country. Regardless of where these activities occur, we take appropriate steps to ensure that your information is protected consistent with the principles set forth under this Privacy Statement.
Who has access to the personal information?
We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other customer data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except our approved agents and contractors, or as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement.
We rely on some of our affiliates for support of the products and services we offer, and we share some of our back-office functions with other companies. Our affiliates are all required to preserve the confidentiality of any personal information they may access.
We will not disclose any personal information or information about your usage of our websites to unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to service the account, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our obligations to content and technology providers, or as required by law.
How may I correct, amend or delete my personal information, or update my preferences?
You may cancel your registration or update your preferences at any time simply by contacting us.
If you do not want to receive information about our products or services, please contact us.
If you have any additional questions or concerns related to this statement and/or our practices, please contact us at:
Schwartz Injury Law
14496 John Humphrey Drive, Suite 100Orland Park, IL 60462
Phone: 708-226-9000Fax: 708-226-9930
Practice Areas
Personal InjuryCar AccidentsTruck AccidentsSpeedingDUI and Drug UseDriver FatigueShifting or Lost Cargo LoadImproperly Loaded or Maintained TruckMotorcycle AccidentsConstruction AccidentsCatastrophic InjuriesMedical MalpracticeBirth InjuriesCerebral PalsyBrain InjuryHypoxiaMeconium AspirationInfant DeathErbs PalsyMisdiagnosisMedication and Pharmacy ErrorsNursing Home Abuse & NegligenceElder AbuseBed SoresExploitationDefective ProductsDefective Medical ProductsPremises LiabilityDog BitesSlip and FallDay Care AccidentsWrongful Death
Recent Blog Posts
Common Causes of Truck Accidents in Illinois
How Are Witnesses Used in a Personal Injury Claim?
Liability for Injuries Caused by Snow and Ice in Illinois
4 Common Forms of Elder Abuse in Nursing Homes
What Types of Compensation Are Available in a Personal Injury Claim Involving Catastrophic Injuries?
Orland Park Office
14496 John Humphrey DriveSuite 100Orland Park, IL 60462Phone: 708-226-9000
Elmhurst Office
360 West Butterfield RoadSuite 300Elmhurst, IL 60126Phone: 630-415-0500
Glen Ellyn Office
519 N. Main Street, Unit 1BNGlen Ellyn, IL 60137Phone: 630-273-7330
Joliet Office
58 N. Chicago Street, 7th FloorJoliet, IL 60432Phone: 815-723-7300
HOME
FIRM OVERVIEW
ATTORNEY PROFILES
PRACTICE AREAS
TESTIMONIALS
BLOG
CONTACT US
From our office in Orland Park, Illinois, we handle matters in areas of Cook County including Chicago, Chicago Ridge, Glenview, Crestwood, Orland Park, Evergreen Park, Bedford Park, Palos Park, Oak Lawn, Burbank, Oak Forest, Blue Island, Elmhurst, Palos Heights, Palos Hills, Alsip, Bridgeview, Lemont, Orland Hills, Country Club Hills, Hickory Hills, Summit, Richton Park, Midlothian, Worth, Posen, Matteson, Olympia Fields, Hometown, and Tinley Park, in DuPage County areas including Downers Grove, Glen Ellyn, Naperville, Woodridge, and Darien, in Kane County areas including Aurora, Elgin and Geneva, and the Will County cities of Joliet, Bolingbrook, Mokena, Frankfort, New Lenox, Lockport, Homer Glen, Romeoville, and Manhattan.
© 2020 Schwartz Injury Law14496 John Humphrey Drive, Suite 100, Orland Park, IL 60462708-226-9000
Resources |
Disclaimer |
Privacy Policy |
Sitemap
